(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(17)},17:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(1),s=n(2),r=n(4),o=n(3),i=n(5),c=n(0),u=n.n(c),l=n(8),d=n.n(l),h=(n(7),n(9)),m=n.n(h),q=(n(16),function(e){function t(){return Object(a.a)(this,t),Object(r.a)(this,Object(o.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(i.a)(t,e),Object(s.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return u.a.createElement("div",null,u.a.createElement("h1",{className:"question"},this.props.text))}}]),t}(c.Component)),w=function(e){function t(){return Object(a.a)(this,t),Object(r.a)(this,Object(o.a)(t).apply(this,arguments))}return Object(i.a)(t,e),Object(s.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){return u.a.createElement("div",null,u.a.createElement("h1",{className:"score"},"You scored ",this.props.text,"/",this.props.total))}}]),t}(c.Component),y=n(10),g=function(e){var t=e.options,n=e.selected,a=Object(c.useState)(t),s=Object(y.a)(a,2),r=s[0],o=s[1];return u.a.createElement("div",null,r.map((function(e,t){return u.a.createElement("button",{key:t,className:"answerBtn",onClick:function(){n(e),o([e])}},e)})))},b=[{question:"Leeds, United Kingdom is the birthplace of what Borussen?",answers:["Marwin Hitz","Jadon Sancho","Manuel Akanji","Erling Braut Haaland"],correct:"Erling Braut Haaland",questionId:"000001"},{question:"Dan-Axel Zagadou was born in",answers:["Braga, Protugal","Paris, France","Cr\xe9teil, France","Le Blanc-Mesnil, France"],correct:"Cr\xe9teil, France",questionId:"000002"},{question:"With 127 goals, this player is 7th on Dortmund's all-time top 10 goalscorers",answers:["Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang","Marco Reus","J\xfcrgen Sch\xfctz","Lothar Emmerich"],correct:"Marco Reus",questionId:"000003"},{question:"Nuri Sahin became the Bundesliga's youngest scorer at what age?",answers:["16 years & 238 days","17 years & 82 days","16 years & 334 days","17 years & 37 days"],correct:"17 years & 82 days",questionId:"000004"},{question:"What year did the Westfalenstadion open?",answers:["1972","1978","1974","1975"],correct:"1974",questionId:"000005"},{question:"Ewerthon scored the goal to give Borussia Dortmund the lead over Bremen after only being on for _____.",answers:["1 minute 4 seconds","49 seconds","1 minute 23 seconds","38 seconds"],correct:"49 seconds",questionId:"000006"},{question:"Borussia Dortmund finished at the top of the table with ____ in the 11/12 season.",answers:["81 points","75 points","78 points","80 points"],correct:"81 points",questionId:"000007"},{question:"Cruising to a 4-1 victory, beating which team in the final of the 1988-89 DFB-Pokal?",answers:["VfB Stuttgart","FC Bayern","Werder Bremen","Bayer 04"],correct:"Werder Bremen",questionId:"000008"},{question:"After how many years did Borussia Dortmund get their first win against Sch*lke?",answers:["18","3","7","23"],correct:"18",questionId:"000009"},{question:"With 10 goals this player is the top time scorer in the Revierderby?",answers:["Ingo Anderbr\xfcgge","Michael Zorc","Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang","Lothar Emmerich"],correct:"Lothar Emmerich",questionId:"000010"},{question:"Which player is a noted Dragon Ball fan?",answers:["Hakimi","Zaga","Sancho","Dahoud"],correct:"Zaga",questionId:"000011"},{question:"This player is red-green colorblind?",answers:["Julian Brandt","Roman B\xfcrki","Thomas Delaney","Marco Reus"],correct:"Thomas Delaney",questionId:"000012"},{question:"Which player was not apart of the 10/11 champion team",answers:["Ilkay G\xfcndogan","Lukasz Piszczek","Mario G\xf6tze","Mitchell Langerak"],correct:"Ilkay G\xfcndogan",questionId:"000013"},{question:"Which player was not in the 94/95 champion team?",answers:["Andreas M\xf6ller","Stefan Klos","Matthias Sammer","Marco Kurz"],correct:"Marco Kurz",questionId:"000014"},{question:"Lucien Favre was born in",answers:["Wiesendangen, Switzerland","Saint-Barthelemy, Switzerland","M\xfcnsingen, Switzerland","St. Gallen, Switzerland"],correct:"Saint-Barth\xe9lemy, Switzerland",questionId:"000015"},{question:"Lucien Favre became the first ever manager to remain unbeaten for how many Bundesliga matches",answers:["10","20","15","18"],correct:"15",questionId:"000016"},{question:"What is the capacity of the Westfalenstadion?",answers:["81365","81455","81220","81565"],correct:"81365",questionId:"000017"},{question:"Borussia Dortmund returned to the Bundesliga in?",answers:["1973","1975","1976","1978"],correct:"1976",questionId:"000018"},{question:"Which company has not been a supplier of Dortmund kits?",answers:["Adidas","Nike","Kappa","Umbro"],correct:"Umbro",questionId:"000019"},{question:"B\u0142aszczykowski was plagued by a torn leg muscle in which season?",answers:["2008-09","2009-10","2010-11","2012-13"],correct:"2008-09",questionId:"000020"},{question:"On 1 August 2016 B\u0142aszczykowski joined Wolfsburg for?",answers:["\u20ac4 million ","\u20ac8 million","\u20ac5 million","\u20ac12 million"],correct:"\u20ac5 million",questionId:"000021"},{question:"Shinji Kagawa initially joined Borussia Dortmund for?",answers:["\u20ac3.5 million","\u20ac350,000","\u20ac700,000","\u20ac5 million"],correct:"\u20ac350,000",questionId:"000022"},{question:"Christian Pulisic joined Chelsea in 2019 for a fee of?",answers:["\u20ac64 million","\u20ac50 million","\u20ac46 million","\u20ac75 million"],correct:"\u20ac64 million",questionId:"000023"},{question:"When is Marco Reus' birthday?",answers:["October 31","July 6","February 29","May 31"],correct:"May 31",questionId:"000024"},{question:"Which manager signed Guerreiro?",answers:["Tuchel","St\xf6ger","Favre","Bosz"],correct:"Tuchel",questionId:"000025"},{question:"How fast did Erling Haaland score a hattrick on his debut?",answers:["45 minutes","23 minutes","36 minutes","12 minutes"],correct:"23 minutes",questionId:"000026"},{question:"How many appearances did Matthias Sammer make for Borussia Dortmund?",answers:["115","75","200","25"],correct:"115",questionId:"000027"},{question:"Which manager led Dortmund to their title in 2002?",answers:["Udo Lattek","Matthias Sammer","Lucien Favre","Bert van Marwijk"],correct:"Matthias Sammer",questionId:"000028"},{question:"What is Mats Hummels middle name?",answers:["Jakob","Mats","Julian","Martin"],correct:"Julian",questionId:"000029"},{question:"How many goals did Jadon Sancho score in the 2018-19 season?",answers:["10","16","14","12"],correct:"12",questionId:"000030"},{question:"When did Gio Reyna make is BVB debut?",answers:["February 4, 2020","January 24, 2020","January 18, 2020","February 5, 2020"],correct:"January 18, 2020",questionId:"000031"},{question:"Which year was the Revierderby born?",answers:["1925","1909","1927","1918"],corect:"1925",questionId:"000032"},{question:"When did Borussia Dortmund begin wearing black and yellow",answers:["1963","1909","1925","1913"],correct:"1913",questionId:"000033"},{question:"In the 2012-13 season, how many goals did Robert Lewandowski score?",answers:["20","24","26","17"],correct:"24",questionId:"000034"},{question:"Emre Can was born in which German city?",answers:["Munich","Berlin","Frankfurt am Main","Leipzig"],correct:"Frankfurt am Main",questionId:"000035"},{question:"Which team has Emre Can not played for?",answers:["Manchester United","Bayer Leverkusen","Bayern Munich","Juventus"],correct:"Manchester United",questionId:"000036"},{question:"With which club did Jadon Sancho begin his career?",answers:["Manchester City","Arsenal","Southampton","Watford"],correct:"Watford",questionId:"000037"},{question:"Which Dortmunder was not in the 2014 WC German squad?",answers:["Kevin Grosskreutz","Erik Durm","Marco Reus","Mats Hummels"],correct:"Marco Reus",questionId:"000038"},{question:"In 2016-17 Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang was the Bundesliga leading scorer with how many goals?",answers:["29","31","32","27"],correct:"31",questionId:"000039"},{question:"Borussia Dortmund won the 2016-17 DFB-Pokal with what score?",answers:["1-0","2-0","2-1","3-2"],correct:"2-1",questionId:"000040"},{question:"Erling Haalands initial contract with BVB is set to end in what year?",answers:["2022","2023","2024","2025"],correct:"2024",questionId:"000041"},{question:"How tall is Dan-Axel Zagadou?",answers:["190 cm","196 cm","198 cm","189 cm"],correct:"196 cm",questionId:"000042"},{question:"What are the original colors of BVB?",answers:["Blue & White","Red & Blue","Black & Yellow","Green & Black"],correct:"Blue & White",questionId:"000043"},{question:"Who wore the captain's armband the longest?",answers:["Lothar Huber","Michael Zorc","Marcel Schmelzer","Sebastian Kehl"],correct:"Michael Zorc",questionId:"000044"},{question:"Borussia Dortmund suffered the biggest defeat in the Bundesliga with what scoreline?",answers:["9-0","12-0","20-2","12-1"],correct:"12-0",questionId:"000045"},{question:"In which season were Dortmund not Bundesliga champions?",answers:["1965-66","1995-96","1961-62","2010-11"],correct:"1965-66",questionId:"000046"},{question:"How many times have Dortmund wont the DFB-Pokal?",answers:["7 times"," 4 times","3 times","2 times"],correct:"4 times",questionId:"000047"},{question:"When did Watzke become CEO",answers:["February 2005"," December 2004","July 2004","July 2005"],correct:"February 2005",questionId:"000048"},{question:"Stadion Rote Erde was the first team stadium until when?",answers:["1974","1976","1995","1982"],correct:"1974",questionId:"000049"},{question:"How many appearances did Roman Weidenfeller make for BVB?",answers:["355","350","349","301"],correct:"349",questionId:"000050"}],p=function(e){function t(){var e,n;Object(a.a)(this,t);for(var s=arguments.length,i=new Array(s),c=0;c<s;c++)i[c]=arguments[c];return(n=Object(r.a)(this,(e=Object(o.a)(t)).call.apply(e,[this].concat(i)))).state={questionBank:[],score:0,responses:0,questionNum:0,q:"",answers:[],id:0,selectedA:"",totalQs:7,showScore:!1,qID:[],questionId:"",qToGet:"",qArray:[]},n.getQNumber=function(){n.state.qToGet=Math.floor(50*Math.random())+1,n.getQToAsk()},n.getQToAsk=function(){n.state.qArray.includes(n.state.qToGet)&&n.getQNumber(),n.state.qArray=n.state.qID.concat(n.state.qToGet)},n.getQuestions=function(){n.getQNumber();var e=b[n.state.qToGet];try{var t=e.answers.sort((function(){return.5-Math.random()}));n.state.answers=t,n.state.questionId=e.questionId,n.state.correct=e.correct,n.state.q=e.question,n.state.qID=n.state.qArray,n.state.questionBank=[]}catch(a){n.getQuestions()}},n.checkAnswer=function(e,t,a,s){a!==s&&s!==a||(e++,n.state.score=e),n.setState({score:e}),t++,n.state.responses=t,n.checkGame(t)},n.playAgain=function(){n.setState({responses:0,score:0,showScore:!1,qArray:[]}),n.getQuestions()},n}return Object(i.a)(t,e),Object(s.a)(t,[{key:"checkGame",value:function(e){e===this.state.totalQs&&this.setState({showScore:!0}),this.getQuestions()}},{key:"startGame",value:function(){this.setState({score:0,responses:0,showScore:!1}),this.getQuestions()}},{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){console.log("hey"),this.startGame()}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;switch(this.state.showScore){case!0:return u.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-board"},u.a.createElement(w,{text:this.state.score,total:this.state.totalQs}),u.a.createElement("button",{className:"playBtn",onClick:this.playAgain},"Play Again"));default:return u.a.createElement("div",{className:"mainCon"},u.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},u.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionBox"},u.a.createElement(q,{className:"question",text:this.state.q}),u.a.createElement(g,{options:this.state.answers,key:this.state.questionId,selected:function(t){return e.checkAnswer(e.state.score,e.state.responses,t,e.state.correct)}}))))}}}]),t}(c.Component),f=function(e){function t(){var e,n;Object(a.a)(this,t);for(var s=arguments.length,i=new Array(s),c=0;c<s;c++)i[c]=arguments[c];return(n=Object(r.a)(this,(e=Object(o.a)(t)).call.apply(e,[this].concat(i)))).state={renderView:!1},n.clickBtn=function(e){!1===n.state.renderView?n.setState({renderView:!0}):n.setState({renderView:!1})},n}return Object(i.a)(t,e),Object(s.a)(t,[{key:"render",value:function(){switch(this.state.renderView){case!0:return u.a.createElement(p,null);default:return u.a.createElement("div",{className:"menuCon"},u.a.createElement("h1",{className:"title"},"Dortmund Trivia Quiz"),u.a.createElement("img",{className:"img",alt:"logo",src:m.a}),u.a.createElement("br",null),u.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn",onClick:this.clickBtn},"Start Quiz"))}}}]),t}(c.Component),I=document.getElementById("root");d.a.render(u.a.createElement(f,null),I)},7:function(e,t,n){},9:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n.p+"static/media/Germany_Team_Vector.bd838279.svg"}},[[11,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.8dda53a1.chunk.js.map